Finding aid for the J. Paul Getty Trust Press Releases and Public Outreach Materials, 1954-1959, 1973-2022 (bulk 1983-2022) IA10011
Institutional Records and Archives
- Press releases, subject files, 1974-2002; 2006; Series II.; 7.08 Linear Feet (8 boxes)
  - Getty Research Institute (GRI) / Getty Center for the History of Art and the Humanities (GCHAH)
    - Performances and events:
      - John Cage Performance, November 4, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 37)
        [Includes: Press Release; Calendar Announcement 10/27/1993; Calendar Announcement 10/25/1993; Extended Calendar Announcement/Summary (Draft); Schedule; Flier; Copies from Piano Album]
      - Aesthetics of Community-Based Art (includes Calendar Announcement 2/8/1993), February 12, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 31)
      - Schedule of Events 1993: Asian Heritage Month (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 30)
      - Calendar Announcements and Calendar of Events for 2/19/1992-5/26/1992: Shifting Boundaries 3/2/1992-6/15/1992 (includes list of Lectures/Performances/Panel Discussions/Film/Video) (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 32)
      - Reading and the Arts of the Book, May 27, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 33)
      - Shifting Boundaries/Cont. Spaces (includes Photographing Schedule), February 25, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 34)
    - Projects:
      - Stack Reader Card and Teacher Resource Center, November 9, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 59)
      - Media Advisory: Mapping Boyle Heights, March 20, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 60)
      - GRI, Digital initiatives programming, 1996-1997 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
      - Duplicate Frank Lloyd Wright Archives, October 17, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 61)
  - Getty Center for Education in the Arts (GCEA)/Getty Education Institute (GEI)
    - Appointments, resignations, and visiting scholars:
      - Leilani Lattin Duke Resigns, May 14, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 147)
      - Martin Rosenberg Appointed as Visiting Scholar, April 20, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 148)
      - Mark Slavkin to Join Getty, December 2, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 149)
      - Terry Barrett Appointed Visiting Scholar (1 copy), September 11, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 150)
      - Mary Erickson Appointed Second Visiting Scholar, March 1, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 151)
      - Michael Day Appointed First Visiting Scholar, September 8, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 152)
      - Phillip Dunn Named New Program Officer with Center for Education in the Arts (1 duplicate copy), March 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 153)
    - Grants and awards:
      - Education Reform Program Implemented: Funding by Getty Education Institute and The Annenberg Foundation (duplicate copies), March 12, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 73)
      - The Annenberg Foundation: $4.3 Million Challenge Grant, April 15, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 74)
      - Fact Sheet: 1993-1994 Project Goals for Discipline-Based Art Education/RIG program, October 6, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 75)
      - Nation's Largest Art Education Reform Initiative, October 6, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 76)
      - National School Boards Association Press Release: NSBA Awarded Special Initiative Getty Grant (includes Memorandum 1/30/1990), January 10, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 77)
      - Regional Institute Grant Program Gives $3.75 Million, September 1, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 78)
      - Meeting to Enhance Arts Education in US, April 26-28, 1989, Sarasota, FL (includes Fact Sheets), April 17, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 79)
      - Program to Reform Art Education Curricula, July 29, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 80)
      - Awards to Improve Teacher Education, March 18, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 81)
      - Regional Institute Planning Grant Awards, June 2, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 82)
    - Projects:
      - Eye Spy LA, March 27, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 105)
      - Wave Your Banner, 1996-1997:
        - Wave your Banner Project, May 19, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 83)
        - Deadline Approaches for "Wave Your Banner" (1 duplicate copy), September 26, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 84)
        - Wave your Banner Project, February 8, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 85)
      - ArtsEdNet, 1995-1996:
        - ArtsEdNet Features Jesus Moroles for Online Exhibition, October 18, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 86)
        - ArtsEdNet Features Sandy Skoglund, February 8, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 87)
        - New Web Site Launched, September 19, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 88)
        - ArtsEdNet to Debut in September, July 7, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 89)
      - GOALS 2000, 1995:
        - $200,000 Given to Goals 2000 Leadership Fund, May 16, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 90)
        - Summer Seminars for National Standards for Arts Education (1 duplicate copy), March 17, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 91)
      - The College Board Release: Study Role of Arts in Unifying High School Curriculum, April 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 106)
      - Assorted Correspondence, April 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 107)
        [Note: Includes Memorandum regarding 5/14/1992 Filming; Memorandum regarding RAI-TV Filming, 4/20/1992; Memorandum regarding Michael Kendall aritcle, 2/17/1993 (with associated Emerge Press Clipping); Correspondence to ARTnews regarding "More Than Pumpkins in October: Visual Literacy in the 21st Centruy", 6/18/1992; NPR on KCRW Radio, All Things Considered, Radio Transcript, 3/11/1994]
      - MAPS (Multicultural Art Posters), 1991-1995:
        - Women Artists and Art from India (1 duplicate copy), February 27, 1995; [Includes page with 4 photos] (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 92)
        - Mexican American and Native Amercian Art Posters Published (MAPS) (with 4 photo sheets), November 17, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 93)
        - Multicultural Arts Posters (MAPS) (includes photo sheets), March 25, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 94)
      - Artist in Schools 2nd Year, March 16, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 108)
      - China Art Exhibit, 1989:
        - Children's Art Exhibition to China, April 21, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 103)
        - China Art Exhibition, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 104)
          [Note: Includes List of student artists; Memorandum 4/3/1989 on Children's Art Exhibition; Background information; Duplicate copy of advertising card; Press release 1/3/1989 on Hou Ling's "Observations on American Art Education"; Hou Ling's "Observations on American Art Education"]
      - Expanded Program for 1985 Institute for Educators on the Visual Arts, June 28, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 109)
      - The Place for Art in America's Schools, April 1, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 110)
      - Children and Teacher Programs (TV and Video), 1984-1994:
        - Video Series: "Art Education in Action,", November 9, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 95)
        - Two New Art Education Advocacy Videos, October 20, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 96)
        - Pacific Visions Release: Documentary: Teacher TV: The Art of Learning, March 22, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 97)
        - Public Services Spots with Fox Children's Network, November 23, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 98)
        - Memorandum: Television Special with Discovery Channel on Arts Education (includes flyer), September 16, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 99)
        - Imagination Machines, August 23, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 100)
        - Pacific Visions Release: Arts for Life with Howard Hesseman (duplicate copies) (includes photos), June 6, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 101)
        - Children's Television Series on the Arts: National Endowment for the Arts Press Release (1 duplicate copy) (includes National Endowment for the Arts Program Solicitation 8/1984), September 24, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 102)
    - Conferences:
      - East meets West through Arts Education, Getty sends delegation to Beijing, China: International conference on arts education, October 1998 (Box 2013.IA.66-01)
      - East Meets West through Arts Education, September 25, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 123)
      - Middle-school Students convene for national Kids Congress on Art, October 24, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 124)
      - Arts Education Conference Establishes New Commitment, February 6, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 125)
      - Conference: Educating for the Workplace Through the Arts, December 6, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 126)
      - Media Advisory: Beyond the 3 Rs: Transforming Education with the Arts, August 11, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 127)
      - Assorted correspondence: National Invitational Conference 2/4-6/93, San Francisco, CA, 1992-1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 128)
      - Pacific Visions: National Conference Draws 1,600, February 25, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 129)
      - Pacific Visions Release: National Invitational Conference 2/4-6/1993, San Francisco, CA: "Achieving National Education Reform: Arts Education as Catalyst,", January 21, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 130)
      - Pacific Visions Release: National Invitational Conference 2/4-6/1993: "Achieving National Education Reform: Arts Education as Catalyst", December 4, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 131)
      - Pacific Visions Release: National Invitational Conference 2/4-6/1993: "Achieving National Education Reform: Arts Education as Catalyst,", October 22, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 132)
      - Pacific Visions Media Advisory: 4th Annual National Invitational Conference: "Achieving National Education Reform: Arts Education as Catalyst,", October 15, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 133)
      - Pacific Visions Release "Future Tense: Arts Education Technology" Conference, January 24-26, 1991, January 16, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 134)
      - Pacific Visions Release: "Future Tense: Arts Education Technology" Conference, January 24-26, 1991 (includes Media Advisory), November 8, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 135)
      - Pacific Visions Release: Third National Conference: "Future Tense: Arts Education Technology,", October 15, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 136)
      - Getty Conference Urges Change in Art Education, January 15-17, 1987, Los Angeles (duplicate copies) (includes duplicate copies of Hunt Macmillion Associates Release, 2/9/1987), February 4, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 137)
      - Hunt Marmillion Associates Press Releases, 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 138)
        [Includes: Invitational Conference Release, January 15-17, 1987 (1 copy, 10/14/1986); Agenda for National Conference (1 copy, 12/04/86)]
    - Doctoral fellowships:
      - 1998 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, March 27, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 139)
      - 1997 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, March 14, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 140)
      - 1996 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, May 13, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 141)
      - 1995 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, April 5, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 142)
      - 1994 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, May 27, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 143)
      - 1993 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, April 5, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 144)
      - 1992 Doctoral Fellowships Awarded, April 7-9, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 145)
      - First Doctoral Fellowships (includes Publicity Data Sheet), June 26, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-5, Folder 146)
    - Programs administered by Getty Center for Education in the Arts/Getty Education Institute:
      - Museum Management Institute, 1987-1991; 1999:
        - Participants Named in 20th Annual Museum Management Institute, June 17, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 29)
        - Museum Management Institute 13th Session, June 14, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 30)
        - Museum Management Institute 12th Session, June 29, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 31)
        - Museum Management Institute Grant for Minority Scholarships (cancelled), August 23, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 32)
        - Museum Management Institute 11th Session, July 6, 1989 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 33)
        - Philip Nowlen Named Academic Dean of the Museum Management Institute (includes Update on Creation of Press Release, 4/21/1987), May 8, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 34)
      - Leadership Institute, 1998-2000:
        - Philip Nowlen Named Head of Leadership Institute, October 13, 2000 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 35)
        - Leadership Institute – Summer 1998 Session, May 15, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 36)
      - Art on Film, 1984-1997:
        - Six Experimental Films, September 14, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 1)
        - Expanded Website: Art on Film Online (includes Pratt Institute Release 9/16/1996), November 10, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 2)
        - $500,000 to Columbia Univeristy School of the Arts, April 30, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 3)
        - Art Museums and Media, March 22, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 4)
        - Architecture on Screen, February 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 5)
        - Architecture Film Festival at Metropolitan Museum, February 26, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 6)
        - Nadine Covert Biography, July 9, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 7)
        - Brown Bag Lunch Movie Series, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 8)
          [Note includes: Memorandum and Program Information, 1/4/1993 and 2/3/1993]
        - Art on Film Information Kit for New Video Series 1992, August 31, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 9)
          [Includes: Press Release; Copies of Photos with Captions; Video Series Program; Screening Schedule; Credits; Program Notes; Quotes]
        - New Video Series, August 31, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 10)
        - Art on Film: Film on Art, June 30, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 11)
        - Art on Screen Newsletter, May 26, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 12)
        - Art on Screen Directory, May 26, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 13)
        - London Premier for PFAF Productions, May 15, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 14)
        - Art on Film Workshop (includes Information Sheet), February 27, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 15)
        - Information Sheet: Program for Art on Film, November 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 16)
        - Sound and Images Conference, February 8, 1991; May 14, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 17)
        - Database Service Launched, January 11, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 18)
        - Database Information Kit, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 19)
          [Includes: Films on Art Bibliography; Information Sheet; Information Sheet--Research Service; Information Request Form; Information Sheet--The Critical Inventory of Films and Video on the Visual Arts; Enrollment Mailer]
        - Database Service Launched, December 4, 1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 20)
        - PFAF and Metropolitan Musuem Joint Venture Completes First Films, September 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 21)
        - Production Laboratory Progress Report, January 23, 1987 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 22)
        - Information Sheet: The Production Laboratory (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 23)
        - Information Sheet: Note on the Ideas for Production Laboratory (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 24)
        - Critical Inventory Progress Report, December 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 25)
        - Information Sheet: Program for Art on Film, June 1986 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 26)
        - Information Sheet: Program for Art on Film, November 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 27)
        - Metropolitan Museum and PFAF Joint Venture (includes Metropolitan Museum Release 3/1984), February 27, 1984; March 8, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 28)
  - Art History Information Program (AHIP)/Getty Information Institute (GII)
    - Appointments:
      - Eleanor Fink Appointed Director of Art History Information Program (Includes Eleanor Fink Biography 8/1994), November 17, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 61)
      - Michael Ester Named Director for Art History Information Program, January 9, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 62)
      - Draft of Columbia University Release: Announcement of James Kopp as Editor of the Avery Index, June 26, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 63)
    - Bibliographic and research databases:
      - Art History Information Program Databases, March 1, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 57)
      - Census, 1992:
        - Census Release (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 43)
          [Includes: Questions for the Census Retrieval System; Photo of Dr. Arnold Nellelrath; Caption]
        - Unique Art-Historical Database and Retrieval System (includes Fact Sheet: The Census of Antique Art and Architecture Known to the Renaissance), March 20, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 44)
      - Provenance Index, 1994-1996:
        - Getty Provenance Index Cumulative Edition on CD-ROM (Duplicate copy), October 15, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 41)
        - Compact Disk Documents the History of Collecting, December 7, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 42)
      - Bibliography of the History of Art (BHA), 1991:
        - Pacific Visions Release: Bibliography of the History of Art, February 21, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 39)
        - Pacific Visions Media Advisory: Publication of Bibliography of the History of Art (French/English), February 7, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 40)
        - Single Bibliographic Database Agreement with France's National Center, May 28, 1985 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 59)
    - Conferences:
      - Museums and the Web: An International Conference (includes Conference Overview, Workshops, and Conference at a Glance), March 13, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 55)
      - Technology, Scholarship, and the Humanities: Scholars Urged to Take Action on New Information Technologies (includes Memorandum 8/5/1993: Discussion Centered Around Summary of Proceedings), July 7, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 46)
      - Future of Information Technology, October 21, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 47)
      - Forum on Information Technology Considers Strategies for Collaboration, September 24, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 48)
    - Standards and vocabularies:
      - Art and Architecture Thesaurus (AAT), 1992:
        - Database of Folk Art to Test Standards, February 14, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 58)
        - The Art and Architecture Thesaurus: Authority Reference Tool Edition (includes Cover Letter 9/15/1992), September 15, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 45)
      - Imaging Initiative, 1993-1994:
        - Intellectual Property Rights Related to Digital Images in Information, December 23, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 49)
        - Humanities and Arts on the Information Highways, September 2, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 50)
        - Initiative on Digital-Imaging Standards, August 31, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 51)
        - National Initiative to Influence National Information Infrastructure, February 7, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 52)
          [Includes: Press Release; Draft of Internet Press Release, 1/19/1984; Official Memorandum to Department Heads, 2/1/1994; Press Clipping; Dr. Cora Bagley Marrett Biography]
        - Getty and Kodak Announce New Company, Luna Imaging, to Develop Digital Collections for the Arts, June 4, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 53)
          [Includes: Press Release; Kodak Press Release 6/7/1993 on Advantages of Imaging in the Visual Arts; Fact Sheet about Luna Imaging; Memorandum 6/1/1993 about Michael Ester to head Luna Imaging]
      - Protecting Cultural Objects, 1992-1993:
        - Object ID Checklist and Video (1 duplicate copy), March 25, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 54)
        - Worldwide Art Theft Report: Protecting Cultural Objects through International Documentation Standards (includes two diskettes), August 17, 1995 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 56)
        - Duplicate Copies of Press Releases from the Research Libraries Group, Inc, 1985-1990 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 60)
          [Includes: 3/16/1990, Vatican Archives Accessible through RLIN; 6/22/1990, Art and Architecture Now Only in RLIN; 10/6/1989, Retrospective Avery Index Records On-Line; 4/10/1987, Brandeis Doing Herbraica Recon Project in RLIN; 3/27/1987, NEH/Luce Foundation Grant $270,000 to RLG for Chinese Preservation Microfilming; 2/13/1987, William P. Timlake is New President of RLG; 2/13/1987, ICPSR Shares Social Sciences Information Through RLIN; 1/18/1987, RLG Provides Gateway to Dialog on RLIN Computer; 12/6/1985, RLG Inaugurates Transatlantic Link with British Library; 12/6/1985, Grant from NHPRC for Cooperative Project with 7 State Archives; 6/21/1985, British Library Sets Transatlantic Link; 3/15/1985, Carnegie Corporation Funds RLIN Network Server; 3/15/1985, IBM PC Versions of RLIN Terminal; 3/15/1985, Grant from NEH for Retrospective Conversion of Archival Records]
    - Projects:, 1996-1997:
      - LA Culture Net, 1996-1997:
        - LA Culture Net, April 17, 1997 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 37)
          [Includes: Release about Landmark Online Resource; Introduction to Project; Fact Sheet of "Faces of LA"; Fact Sheet of LA Culture Net; Fact Sheet of Break Away Technologies]
        - LA Culture Net Web Site to Create a Model Digital Community (includes Fact Sheet), September 18, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 38)
  - Foundation:
    - Appointments, awards, and resignations:
      - Announcement: Deborah Marrow, Director of the Getty Grant Program, September 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 116)
      - Grant Program Announced, October 11, 1984 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 117)
    - Grants:
      - Preserve LA, December 20, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 16)
      - Microgallery in Prague, February 1, 1999; February 8, 1999 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 64)
      - Save America's Treasures, December 10, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 65)
      - Grants Promote Innovative Collaborations, August 7, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 66)
      - Historic Little Rock Central High School Conservation Plan, February 9, 1998 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 67)
      - Conservation of Aachen Cathedral, October 17, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 68)
      - Conservation Survey of Santa Maria Maggiore Mosaics Funded, April 4, 1996 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Flatfile 69)
      - $75,000 Awarded for Preservation of African-American Landmarks, February 17, 1994; (includes Photos) (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 70)
      - CalArts $2 Million for Earthquake Recovery, February 1, 1994; February 7, 1994 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 17)
      - $250,000 for Conservation of Camposanto Monumentale at Pisa, November 8, 1993 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 71)
      - Grant to LA Arts Recovery Fund, August 12, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 18)
      - Grant to LA Library for Riot Destruction, June 17, 1992 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 19)
      - Central and Eastern European Arts Library Grants//New Fellowship Competition, July 12, 1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 72)
      - 23 Architectural Conservation Grants Awarded since 1/1989, April 3, 1990; (includes Photos) (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 73)
      - First Architectural Conservation Grants, December 20, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 74)
      - New Category to Support Architectural Conservation, April 18, 1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-6, Folder 75)
      - Fund for the Visual Arts and the California Community Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 20)
        [Note: Includes 1/8/1991 Release on Grant Reception; 6/14/1990 Release on Grants to 19 LA Artists/Organizations; 12/21/1988 List of 1990 Award Recipients and List of 1989 Grant Recipents; 1988 Application Form; 2/1988 Fact Sheet on California Community Foundation Statement of Purpose; Press Clipping]
      - Gifts to LA Institutions, California Community Foundation, 1987-1988 (Box 2007.IA.34-1, Folder 21)